youripfast.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Find Your IP Fast collects _non-personally-identifying_ information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, your language preference, the referring site, the date and time of each request, and any Javascript errors that occur during your visit. Find Your IP Fast’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Find Your IP Fast’s visitors use its website so we can make improvements and fix bugs. From time to time, Find Your IP Fast may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Find Your IP Fast avoids collecting potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses except to the extent necessary to provide certain services. For example, our site needs to collect an IP address from you for the sole purpose of constructing a webpage containing that IP address and delivering it back to your computer. In this instance your IP address is only stored on our server in temporary memory (RAM) for only as long as is necessary to construct the webpage and deliver it to your computer. We do not store IP addresses in permanent memory (disk), nor are they viewed by any person at Find Your IP Fast. 

### Aggregated Statistics

Find Your IP Fast may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Find Your IP Fast may monitor the most popular pages on findyouripfast.com sites. Find Your IP Fast may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Find Your IP Fast does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Google App Engine

Some of Find Your IP Fast's services may be provided by Google App Engine, a service operated by Google (a third party service provider). As such, you should assume that any information you provide to Find Your IP Fast may be available to Find Your IP Fast and to Google. For details about the specific privacy guarantees made by Google in its capacity as a service provider, please refer to [code.google.com/appengine/privacy.html](http://code.google.com/appengine/privacy.html).

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Find Your IP Fast discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Find Your IP Fast’s behalf or to provide services available at Find Your IP Fast’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Find Your IP Fast’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Find Your IP Fast will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Find Your IP Fast discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Find Your IP Fast believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Find Your IP Fast, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Find Your IP Fast website and have supplied your email address, Find Your IP Fast may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Find Your IP Fast and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Find Your IP Fast takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Find Your IP Fast uses cookies to help Find Your IP Fast identify and track visitors, their usage of Find Your IP Fast website, and their website access preferences. Find Your IP Fast visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Find Your IP Fast’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Find Your IP Fast’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Javascript Errors

Find Your IP Fast’s software products are complex. Occasionally, error conditions which we did not anticipate may occur. If such an error condition occurs on your computer, we may log a small amount of non-personally-identifying information about the error in order to help our engineers prevent it from occurring again.

### Business Transfers

If Find Your IP Fast, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Find Your IP Fast goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of Find Your IP Fast may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. Except in the section "Advertiser Cookies" immediately below, this Privacy Policy discusses the use of cookies by Find Your IP Fast and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. For more information about advertiser cookies you should consult the privacy policies of the specific advertising networks you wish to learn more about.

### Advertiser Cookies

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to the Find Your IP Fast website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads based on your visit to the Find Your IP Fast site and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/). 

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Find Your IP Fast may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Find Your IP Fast’s sole discretion. Find Your IP Fast encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Thanks for reading our privacy policy. Don't forget to check out [Automattic](http://automattic.com/), purveyors of only the finest web software. For example, [Wordpress](http://www.wordpress.com/) is a handy free blog service with reasonably-priced upgrades. 

This privacy policy is licensed under the [Creative Commons](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0/).
